Downloaded from
YTS.BZ
Official YIFY movies site:
[gentle music playing]
[Ry] My body has become my enemy.
But here I am,
just another particle of the Earth.
The ocean doesn't care about sickness
or life and death.
It doesn't care for
our struggles or our pain.
Or that I would have given everything...
...for one last summer like this.
One last sunrise...
...with him.
[♪ Kye Kye sings "People"]
♪ ♪
♪ I still yearn to be ♪
♪ love without a need to please ♪
♪ Help me, help me ♪
♪ Silent crave to have childish peace ♪
♪ while weary things ♪
- [ears ringing, heart beating]
- ♪ haunt me, haunt me ♪
- ♪ Like falling in my sleep...
- [breathes shakily]
[music continues low and distorted]
[shallow gasping]
Ry. Ry.
- [shallow gasping continues]
- [heart beating faster]
[tense music playing]
Ry!
Move, move, move!
I got her. Okay.
Okay, breathe.
Breathe, Ry.
You got to breathe, sweetheart.
At this stage, Oriah,
I would strongly recommend surgery.
There's still a chance
we can remove all the tubers,
and you could be seizure-free.
And there's an equal chance
that I'll lose my memory.
People, places, how to walk,
how to dance, how to live.
Everything that makes me a person.
Ry, this is your life we're talking about.
Exactly, Mom. It's my life.
Okay, we could increase the medication,
but it'll most likely increase
the side effects.
I would set alarms
so you don't miss a dose,
or they won't work properly.
Can you commit to that?
Ry. Ry.
Honey, I know they make you
feel like shit.
Correction.
They don't let me feel anything.
All right, Lena, be sure to book a driver
to take her
- wherever she wants to go.
- Yeah.
Also, there's a pharmacy
two streets over from the hotel
where you can fill her prescription.
Other than that,
it's just the usual things
we need to be mindful of
with her epilepsy:
flashing lights, get good sleep,
no stress, no alcohol.
Great. The nuns and I will be having
our hot girl summer.
So, days one through four are super busy
with the location manager
and Redwyn attorneys.
I'll try to schedule some time off, but--
What about spending time together?
Mom, you promised to show me
where you grew up.
No, honey, we are gonna spend
lots of time together.
We have six whole weeks.
We're gonna have fun. It's Mallorca.
As long as you keep your promise.
Thank you.
All right, let me see that schedule again.
[Lena] Yes.
[♪ Sofia Kourtesis sings "Madres"]
[song continues with lyrics in Spanish]
[tires screech]
♪ ♪
Hola.
[hotel manager] Welcome.
We're expecting you, Miss Pera.
- Oh, call me Isolde. Hi.
- Welcome.
Muchas gracias. Thank you.
This is my daughter Oriah. Honey.
- Hi.
- She's a bit jet-lagged.
- Why don't you get settled,
and I'll meet you in the room, okay?
I have a quick conference call.
[hotel manager] Our concierge team
is looking forward
- to meeting you.
- [indistinct chatter]
[Amara German accent] Hi there,
and welcome to our hotel.
- Hi.
- How was your flight?
- It was fine.
- Good.
Oh, sorry, you have a little something.
Ah! [chuckles]
I saw it on TikTok.
This took me 20 minutes.
Tell me, honestly,
is it worth investing the time
on the other eye?
Given it's company time,
I'd say yes. [chuckles]
Mm. I like you.
Follow me. Right,
I'll show you to your room.
This way.
- [Amara] I'm Amara, by the way.
- [Ry] I'm Ry.
[Amara] Okay, so this is the lobby.
You can come find me here
anytime you need.
So, what brings you
to our Spanish paradise?
- My mom's closing a real estate deal.
- Uh-huh?
Yeah, her company wants
to build a new hotel.
[gasps] Ooh, another hotel. How exciting.
The locals are gonna love that.
Do you know the island at all?
No. No, it's my first time.
I haven't really been out of Texas much.
Wow, a Texan. How exotic.
So, Ry, what do you like to do for fun?
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe go to the beach or lie by the pool.
You can definitely do that,
but there's tons of other stuff.
- Do you like caves?
- Caves?
[Amara] Are you single?
- Yeah.
- Ugh, the locals here are superhot.
They're like this crazy mix
of Carthaginians, then Romans,
then the Catalan settlers
from France and Spain.
Whatever you are into,
it's like a hookup buffet.
Oh, and don't be surprised
if you see goats in trees.
- Goats in trees?
- Yes, goats in trees.
Anyway, the point is,
you're going to have a summer
worth remembering.
Okay, your mother's room
is just across the hall,
and this one's you.
[gentle music playing]
Your mother's company built
an amazing place.
Yeah.
[phone alarm beeping and vibrating]
Sorry.
- [alarm stops]
- I'll let you settle in.
Just give us a call downstairs
if you need anything at all.
Auf Wiedersehen. Bye-bye.
- Thank you, Amara.
- [door closes]
[pills rattle]
[bottle closes]
- [waves rolling]
- [seagulls calling]
[Ry] So, what's the plan for tomorrow?
[Isolde] I'm packed.
I have back-to-back meetings
and party planning.
What party?
A fundraiser.
Yeah. In addition to getting them
to let us build the hotel,
in good faith,
we are building an arts center
- for the children of Mallorca.
- That's nice.
[phone chimes]
Everything okay?
Just the-the company. [sighs]
They're checking in
to see if I'll return this fall.
But you are going back, right?
You just need to rest this summer.
And then you're gonna be
back in the saddle.
Yeah.
[Chloe over phone] We're all going out
tonight to celebrate
the end of the season.
We wish you were here.
How are you feeling?
Is the new medication helping?
Uh, it's... [chuckles]
it's an adjustment for sure.
We've all been so worried about you.
First of all, don't do that.
Second, I am fine.
My mom has this whole thing
planned for tomorrow.
She's gonna show me where she grew up.
Your mom is such a queen.
And forget what I said.
I wish we were all there with you guys.
Mm-hmm.
Well, tell me
if you see any hot Spaniards.
- Okay?
- Yeah. For sure.
- We love you, babes. Call me!
- [chuckles]
- [women] See you, Ry!
- Love you.
- Love you. Bye.
- [women] Bye.
[phone alarm beeping and vibrating]
- [sighs]
- [alarm stops]
[gentle guitar music playing]
[sputters lips]
♪ ♪
[splashing and laughter in distance]
[splashing and laughter continue]
[guard] Hey! [shouts in Spanish]
[urgent Spanish chatter]
[birds chirping]
[Isolde] Okay, so we have
around 150 guests.
Ooh, this is pretty.
Hey, Ry, do you like eggshell or oatmeal?
Why do they all have to be
named after food?
[Isolde] I don't know.
[sighs] Honey, why don't you go
do something fun,
and I'll meet up with you later.
- I was gonna hit the beach.
- Well, that's a good idea.
Take the driver. Oh!
And extra meds. And water.
And put some sunblock, sweetheart.
- Oh, and, Ry--
- Be careful?
Have fun.
Coconut cream for the win.
[footsteps departing]
See? Pretends not to care, but she does.
Hmm.
- Hi.
Slow morning, was it?
Why?
[chuckles] Your eyes.
- Oh.
- I love the eyeliner.
- Thank you.
- [chuckles]
So, where to?
Oh, actually, yes, I was gonna ask you
if you had any beach recommendations.
I think I know just the spot.
- It's a real hidden gem.
- Ooh.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
Perfect.
[♪ Bad Bunny and The Marias
sing "Otro Atardecer"]
♪ ♪
[quiet chatter]
[song continues with lyrics in Spanish]
♪ ♪
[song fades]
[quiet chatter]
[laughter in distance]
[laughter continues]
[sighs heavily]
["Otro Atardecer" resumes
with lyrics in Spanish]
[laughs]
- [song fades]
- [laughter, quiet chatter]
[gentle music playing]
♪ ♪
[music fades]
Can I help you?
Uh... um, no, no.
It's rude to stare, señorita.
I wasn't... I wasn't staring.
I was just, uh, uh...
I was looking behind you.
[Julian] Wow. Nice view.
[chuckles nervously]
Okay, well, I'm gonna go.
- Yeah, you should go.
- Excuse me?
I said that you should go.
Did I do something?
Uh, do you have a problem?
I do have a problem.
This is a locals' beach.
We prefer when tourists don't
stare at us while we sunbathe.
Uh, I'm so sorry.
I hadn't realized
it was a locals-only beach.
I just wanted to swim.
Well, I think you might find the pool
at the Marès and Mar Hotel more comfortable.
How'd you--
Why?
Am I distracting you?
[stammers] No.
I'm gonna go.
[sighs]
[♪ Billie Eilish sings
"Billie Bossa Nova"]
[singer vocalizing]
♪ Love when it comes without a warning ♪
♪ 'cause waiting for it gets so boring ♪
♪ A lot can change in 20 seconds...
[sighs]
♪ A lot can happen in the dark...
Oh. Hi.
Hola. Do you have a...
Okay.
♪ Some information's not for sharing...
[sighs]
♪ Use different names
at hotel check-ins...
Hola. Excuse me.
¿Hablas inglés?
[in Catalan]
I have many paintings to choose from.
Uh, I need-- Do you have a-a charger?
Maybe right? Or uphill?
- I need your, um--
- I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry. Have a good day. Gracias.
- [grunts]
- [song stops]
- Oh, my God.
- Cabrón.
I'm so sorry.
Listen, señorita.
You can look but not touch.
Do I need to report you?
Don't be ridiculous. I'm on my way home.
So, please, if you'll excuse me.
[sighs]
It's not that way.
It's not that way either.
You are lost, Miss America.
No, I'm not.
I'm just taking in these
beautiful winding streets.
- Mm-hmm.
You can deny it,
or you just can admit it
and ask for my help.
I'm fine.
I'm fine, thank you.
Also, what are you doing?
Are you stalking me?
Oh, yes.
You made such a strong impression
perving on me at the beach.
- [sighs]
- And I just couldn't stay away.
Are you always such a creep?
- Creep?
- Mm.
You know,
actually I was worried about you.
But I have so many things to do,
so my offer to help you
expires in ten seconds.
Diez,
nueve,
ocho,
- siete--
- Fine.
Fine.
Directions to the Marès and Mar Hotel.
You can hold it so you know
I'm not about to murder you.
[gentle music playing]
That way.
- [Ry] It was that way.
- Mm-hmm.
[Ry chuckles]
You know, good-looking men murder women.
Although they're usually quite charming,
so I guess that rules you out.
So you think I'm good-looking?
- [laughs]
- [chuckles]
And I wasn't staring at you earlier.
I was just studying.
Everyone.
Oh, yes.
A new species of naked man
found right here
on the white sand beaches of Mallorca.
There's no nude beaches in Texas.
Oh, really?
Well, then I hope you learned something
new about the human anatomy.
[chuckles softly]
- Hola, Julian.
- [Julian speaks Catalan]
[conversing in Catalan]
- [coins clinking]
- Uh... [sighs]
[conversing in Catalan]
Do you want some?
Uh, no, I'm good.
Come on. I saw you drooling.
- [chuckles]
- Don't be so stubborn.
I'm not stubborn.
Just try it.
Mmm. [chuckles]
We call this ensaïmada.
It's like a... like a croissant.
- But better.
- Much better.
I hadn't realized how hungry I was.
Thank you.
If you want, maybe we could go
and get something to eat.
Are you asking me out?
Nah.
Your hotel has room service.
I hope you enjoy the grass at your hotel.
You have a problem with the grass, too?
Actually, I do.
Did you know that the chemicals used
to keep this grass so green
leak into our water
that we use for fishing?
But just so long as things
are perfect for the tourists,
- who cares, right?
- [chuckles softly]
Like tourists are the worst thing
to ever happen to the island.
Who do you think is buying
the "I love Mallorca" T-shirts
or the key chains? You?
I'm so glad that you know what's the best
for the people of Mallorca.
How long have you been here?
Um...
- One day.
- Huh.
- Yeah, but my mom is from here.
- Is that so?
Mm-hmm.
Well, then forgive me
for doubting your expertise.
Bona nit, senyoreta.
Bye.
[gentle music playing]
[sighs]
[Julian] Hey.
You changed your mind pretty quick.
You couldn't stay away
for more than two minutes?
No, I'd just like my phone back, please.
[softly] Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Adios, señorita.
[Ry] Buenas noches, cabrón.
At least you're learning the language.
[door opens]
[Isolde] Honey, where have you been?
- Are you okay?
- Oh, I'm fine.
Sorry. I went to the beach,
and my phone died.
Your phone died?
Honey, you got to keep your phone charged.
Did you miss taking your pills?
[Isolde groans]
No, Mom, Mom, I took extra meds with me.
It's okay.
All right. I'm sorry.
You know how I worry.
Look at you. You look great.
You got some color,
a little brightness in your eyes.
Tell me everything. What'd you do?
It was chill.
- It was chill?
- [chuckles]
That's it? Just chill?
It was chill, Mom.
But, honestly, with the meds,
I'm kind of zonked.
I just want to pass out.
This dosage is killing me.
Yeah. Okay. All right.
We'll talk tomorrow.
But, hey, I'm so happy you're here.
Still here, you mean?
That's not funny.
Don't make that joke, ever.
All right. Sorry.
Let's talk tomorrow. I love you.
- Get some rest.
- Love you, too.
- Good night.
[sighs heavily]
[phone alarm beeping and vibrating]
[sighs]
[alarm stops]
[gasps] Ry! How was the beach?
You really buried the lede.
Buried what? One second.
They were all naked.
Yeah. That's kind of the whole point.
Did you enjoy it?
The beach and the sea were beautiful.
[scoffs] What about the wildlife?
[chuckles]
I don't know.
- There was this one guy, um, Julian.
- Yeah.
He was a massive dick.
Sorry, he had a massive--
No, no. I heard it, yes.
Uh, he-- I couldn't tell you.
- I didn't look.
- Oh, sure.
He was rude.
Why? What did he do?
He... he walked me back to the hotel
because my phone had died, and he...
he got me food as well.
Yeah, this guy sounds like
a real scoundrel.
You had to be there. I promise you.
I'm teasing.
I know Julian, and, yes, he can be
a bit moody sometimes, but in his defense,
he's got a lot going on right now.
Wait, you know him?
It's a small island, babe.
And based on that face,
you might want to give him
a second chance.
[chuckles]
He and a bunch of us
are going clubbing tonight.
[whispers] You should come.
- To a club?
- Yes.
Big, loud, plays music.
But people will be wearing
their clothes, mostly.
Can I get back to you on that?
No problemo.
Hit me up later.
[whispers] It'll be fun.
Though I can't promise any cowboys.
[chuckles]
- [whispers] Okay, come.
- [woman] Hello.
Hi. Welcome to our hotel.
[Isolde sighs] Oh, God, it's never-ending.
Well, this is fun.
I'm dealing with permits today.
Okay. Tell me, how do you like this place?
- [chuckles] It's beautiful.
- Mm.
It's also really fun to imagine
you as a little kid
just running around the island.
It was amazing growing up here.
Why did you leave?
Once my mom was gone,
it... didn't feel like home anymore.
You know?
And I had big dreams,
and I was on a tiny island.
And to me, this was always her home,
and I wanted to go out and find my own.
And how long did that take?
About five years and nine months.
When you had your precious
little bundle of joy?
No, that's when I had you.
- [laughs]
- [scoffs]
- I'm so funny.
- You're so funny, Mom.
[gentle music playing]
[phone alarm beeping and vibrating]
[alarm stops]
[pensive music playing]
[sighs]
[♪ Sabrina Carpenter sings
"When Did You Get Hot?"]
♪ So long, untouched, bone-dry...
- [Sofia] Ooh.
- Smash or pass?
- No.
- [Ry] Uh, it has a sexy little back.
Ry, no.
No.
♪ Now I'm at the prospect convention ♪
♪ My friends walk...
- Maybe if I, like, tie it.
- [Amara] It's not really
- what I was thinking.
- Sure.
[indistinct chatter]
- [Ry] It's kind of cute.
- [Amara] Immediately no.
- ♪ When did you get hot? ♪
- [indistinct chatter continues]
♪ All the sudden,
I could look you up and down all day ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When did you get hot? ♪
♪ I think I would remember if you had ♪
- ♪ that face ♪
♪ I did a double take, triple take ♪
♪ Take me to naked Twister
back at your place ♪
♪ Baby, baby, mm,
it's thickening the plot...
- [Amara] Yes, Ry!
- [Sofia] Okay.
- Oh, my God!
- Let's do it!
- This is great.
- [gasps]
[indistinct chatter continues]
Oh! Yes, baby. Work it.
♪ Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh ♪
♪ Uh-huh, uh-huh...
Okay, are you coming? Ry!
[♪ Astroboyz sing "Se Menea"]
- [crowd cheering]
- [song continues in Spanish]
- Ah!
- I tried to order three.
- [Amara] Wow!
- [Sofia] Yes, girl!
- But you need to work on your Spanish.
- Oh! We're gonna do shots!
- Un, dos, tres.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Mm.
- Mm.
- [exclaims]
[groans]
- Gosh.
- Oh, Julian!
Come have a shot.
Ry ordered enough for everyone.
[Julian] Hello, girls.
Hello, big spender.
[Amara] I love this song.
Ooh! Who wants to dance?
- [Sofia] Me!
- [Amara] Ry?
[Ry groans]
Come on, chica.
Let's see what you got, Miss America.
[Amara] Let's go, baby.
- [Ry] I'll come with you.
- [Sofia] Ignore him.
¡Venga, venga!
[♪ Kinski Gallo sings "Me Gusta"]
[song continues with lyrics in Spanish]
♪ ♪
[Ry] Stop.
Dude, get off me.
♪ ♪
[crowd cheering]
[song distorting]
[audio muffled]
Hey. [muffled shout]
I got you.
[audio continues clearly]
[panting] Okay.
[sighs] You sure you're okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
I'm fine. I just...
[chuckles] I just can't drink tequila.
Maybe there was something in your drink.
No, no. I'm okay.
Okay, good, 'cause we got to go.
- What?
- Put this on.
- Are we running from people?
- I'll explain later.
I've never ridden a motorcycle.
Oh, really?
Don't worry, you're gonna love it.
[engine starts]
[♪ Karol G sings "Tus Gafitas"]
[song continues with lyrics in Spanish]
You okay?
I'm good.
♪ ♪
I want to show you somewhere.
[song ends]
- You're a fisherman?
- Mm-hmm.
- [chuckles]
- It's my family business.
I grew up on the water.
It's what I know.
One day, I'll take over the fishery
from my dad.
- Hopefully.
- Hopefully?
The fisheries on our island are suffering
because of the tourists
and the commercial companies
are hurting the island.
On the other hand,
it's surviving because of them.
So now you know why I never buy
any of those "I heart Mallorca" shirts.
More people could mean progress.
Mm. [sighs]
Destroying family businesses
doesn't feel like progress.
Mm.
So what about you?
What's waiting for you back in Texas?
[chuckles]
I'm a dancer.
Exotic?
[both chuckle]
- I'm with a company. [chuckles]
- Okay, okay.
But...
I don't even know if I'm going back.
My life back home
just feels like a constant...
loop. [sighs]
Dance is the only thing
that gives it meaning.
And gives me some freedom.
Then why stop?
'Cause it's not up to me anymore.
I'm sorry. My problems
probably sound so trivial.
No, no, no, it's okay.
I mean, rich girls can be sad, too.
We should put that on a T-shirt.
Yeah, we should do that.
[laughs] What are you doing?
Come on.
I can help you if you can't swim.
- I can swim.
- [water splashing]
[gentle music playing]
[chuckles]
[both chuckle]
See? I'm a great swimmer.
I just wanted to make you take
your clothes off this time.
[both laughing]
Oh.
Okay, truce, truce.
[laughing]
- Peace.
This is good.
This summer, I wanted
to try new things, you know?
Live like it's the last summer
I'll ever have.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's a good way to live.
So what's next on your list?
To go to bed without brushing your teeth?
Never.
Or to... not eat your vegetables?
Maybe.
Or to make out with a hot stranger?
I could pretend you're hot.
♪ ♪
[ringtone playing in distance]
[ringtone continues]
Everything okay?
[chuckles] Yeah.
You look beautiful.
You know, you're not that moody.
What?
Just something Amara said.
Come on. I should get you back.
Yeah.
[engine shuts off]
I'm sorry.
I feel like I upset you.
I'm just stressed.
It's about work.
I have a lot going on.
I know.
Can I give you my number?
I... would like that.
- [chuckling]
- If you didn't, I'd feel used.
I'll trade you.
There.
I'll call you.
Okay.
Good night, Oriah.
Good night.
[engine starts]
[insects trilling]
[motorcycle approaching]
[engine shuts off]
You didn't even kiss her good night.
[pensive music playing]
Look, I don't have your money yet, okay?
But I'm working on it.
I'll get it for you.
[grunting]
[coughing]
Of course you'll get it.
[groans, coughs]
'Cause if you don't,
I'll get it from your girlfriend.
She must be pretty rich
if she's staying
in a place like this, huh?
[panting]
[Julian groans]
[grunts, coughs]
[laughing]
Vámonos.
[groans]
[panting]
[car doors closing]
[Isolde] Just finalizing the deal
with the local landowner, but the hotel
will be built.
So, let's talk about you.
Did you take your pills this morning?
Um...
[Ry stammers]
Uh, I'm just still
getting used to the new meds.
You know how it is.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I've been hanging out with Amara.
From the front desk.
Oh, right, yeah, yeah.
And some of her friends.
Well, as long as you're not falling
in love with some hot Spaniard.
[chuckles]
- What? Already?
- [chuckles]
Okay. I'm not even gonna ask.
But if you could peel yourself away
for a couple days,
I could really use your help.
Have your people call my people,
and maybe we'll figure something out.
I'll do that.
- [band playing flamenco music]
- [singer speaking Spanish]
[singing in Spanish]
[talking indistinctly under music]
[chef talking indistinctly under music]
Mmm.
[talking indistinctly under music]
I love the artichoke.
[conversing indistinctly under music]
- [song continues]
- [shoes tapping rhythmically]
[Isolde speaking Spanish]
[talking indistinctly under music]
- [song ends]
- [woman] ¡Olé! ¡Olé!
- Incredible. Oh, my--
- [song resumes]
[singer exclaiming in Spanish]
- Oh.
Oh, my God! Our turn.
- [laughing]
- Get it, Mom.
[both laughing]
[singer continues exclaiming in Spanish]
[song fades]
Ooh, thank God. There you are.
Will you come with me to a bar downtown
for a Tinder date?
[laughs] No.
No, I can't come on a date with you.
Yes. You have to be my safety net
in case she's a serial killer.
You can be our third wheel.
We'll be one big happy tricycle.
Unless of course we get to the good stuff,
then I can be quite possessive.
Go, change! I want to hear
all about Julian the other night.
- [chuckles]
- Go.
So, who is this girl?
Prisha. She's a medical student
visiting from London.
How long is she here for?
Uh, three weeks, I think.
Oh, that's not long.
What if you catch feelings?
Just because something
doesn't last forever
doesn't mean it's not worth experiencing.
And anyway, this is a tourist island.
- People come and go.
- Hmm.
I mean, you won't be here forever,
and you still made out with J.
- Ah! Knew it.
- [laughs]
Locked lips with a scoundrel.
It was just one kiss.
And I haven't heard from him since.
Oh.
Are you that bad of a kisser?
No.
What? I'm just saying.
One kiss then nothing?
No tongue?
[gasps] Too much tongue?
- Oh, God.
- [laughs]
["Sufre Mamón" playing]
[singing in Spanish to music]
[lively chatter]
Well, you've already seen him naked,
so you know what you are getting.
Okay. Oh.
There she is.
- Do you want me to hang back?
- No, no.
She could be dangerous.
- [chuckles]
- Just...
[Amara sighs]
Uh, Prisha?
- Amara. Hi.
- Hi.
[both chuckle]
Uh, this is Ry, my friend from Texas.
- Oh, hi. Lovely to meet you.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
I hope it's not weird that I brought her.
She just doesn't have any friends.
Oh, well, um, I was gonna kidnap you,
but now--
- See?
- Oh, well--
She gets it. Can I get you a drink?
Yes, I would love a drink.
- Would you like one, Ry?
- Uh, yes, please. Thank you.
What do you guys fancy?
I'll do a margarita.
I'm kind of a spicy girl.
Amazing. Excuse me.
Hi. Can we have three margaritas?
Of course.
["Heaven Is a Place on Earth" playing]
[Amara] Ooh, I love this song!
♪ They say, in heaven, love comes first ♪
♪ We'll make heaven a place on Earth ♪
♪ Ooh, heaven is a place on Earth...
You girls look beautiful.
- Wait, I want to remember tonight.
- Okay!
Let's get a photo.
- [phone camera clicks]
- [laughs]
- [audio continues muffled]
- Oh, I love it.
- Are you okay?
- [Amara] So cute.
I'm good.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- [audio continues clearly]
- You girls are so sexy.
[Prisha] Oh, my God, girl, you look so...
[chatter continues indistinctly]
♪ And it carries me ♪
♪ In this world, we're just beginning...
So, are you sensitive to flashing lights?
[chuckles] Yeah.
- Huh.
- Yeah, you could say that.
Um, I have epilepsy.
Oh, okay.
But it's manageable?
- No.
- Oh.
No, mine's pretty terrible.
They really want me
to have surgery, but...
Mm.
there's a big chance
it'll wipe my memory.
And my meds make me feel brain-dead,
so I'm not taking them. [gasps]
[both chuckle]
Well, I know a lot of patients
struggle with that.
[chuckles] I'm sorry.
I don't know why I just told you all that.
I haven't told anyone.
Sometimes it's easier
to talk to a stranger.
[whispers] Thank you.
[gasps dramatically]
Look who just hearted our photo.
- [Prisha] Oh.
- Someone likes what he sees.
That someone ghosted me, Amara.
- He ghosted you?
- Stop that.
- He ghosted me.
- What?
[Amara] Oh, Ry, please.
She just doesn't want to admit
that she's in love.
Okay, I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
- Whoa, look at those abs.
- Mm-hmm.
[lively chatter and laughter]
- [sighs]
- [hands clapping]
She's so good.
- You should come to my boat.
- Your boat?
[Julian] Yeah.
[chatter continues indistinctly]
- ["No Scrubs" playing]
- [Amara] Oh.
[Ry] Thank you.
We'll do it. Tomorrow on the-- Oh.
♪ A scrub is a guy that thinks he's fly ♪
♪ and is also known as a buster ♪
♪ Always talking 'bout what he wants ♪
♪ and just sits on his broke ass ♪
♪ So, no, I don't want your number ♪
♪ No, I don't wanna give you mine ♪
- ♪ And no ♪
- [crowd cheering]
♪ I don't wanna meet you nowhere ♪
♪ No, I don't want none of your time ♪
♪ And no, I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy
that can't get no love from me ♪
- [woman] Go, baby!
- ♪ Hanging out the passenger side ♪
♪ of his best friend's ride ♪
- [whooping]
- ♪ trying to holla at me ♪
[woman whoops, speaks Spanish]
Come on up here.
- ♪ Get the second verse ♪
- [whoops]
- [Prisha] Come on, Amara!
- ♪ He's looking like trash ♪
♪ Can't get with a deadbeat ass ♪
♪ So, no, I don't want your number ♪
♪ No, I don't wanna give you mine ♪
♪ And no,
I don't want to meet you nowhere ♪
♪ I don't want none of your time ♪
[Julian] Ry.
Ry, wait up.
Look, I'm sorry I didn't call you.
Wait, what...
Are you okay?
What happened?
Carlos.
Who's that?
He's a loan shark.
And you owe him money?
Yeah.
- Well, if you need anything--
- Don't insult me
by offering to help.
I didn't call you because
I'm not safe to be around.
Until things are settled
with Carlos, I just...
We have to be careful.
Okay?
Don't worry.
I don't scare that easily.
I like you, Oriah.
[chuckles softly]
I'm only here for a little while.
Then we are wasting time.
[chuckles]
[♪ Bob Moses sings "Last Forever"]
♪ Standing at the bridge ♪
♪ Feel your hand in mine...
[Ry] This is so beautiful.
Yeah.
Very beautiful.
[chuckles]
[Ry] So many people though.
We call them "guiris."
- Wait, what?
- Tourists.
Oh.
- Many, many guiri, then.
- Many, many guiris.
[both chuckle]
Am I a guiri? Do I count? Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, you are a guiri.
- [laughs]
♪ That this will never end...
[Ry laughing]
- Who, back there?
- Yeah.
[laughs] Why are you going?
- ♪ Before it slips away...
- [Amara exclaims]
[laughter]
♪ Wish I could find a way ♪
- ♪ to make it last forever ♪
- [playful chatter]
♪ I know the time will come...
[Ry] Oh, my God.
- [Julian] This is just the beginning.
- [laughs]
♪ Wish I could find a way ♪
♪ to make it last forever ♪
Are we going in that?
♪ Wish I could find a way ♪
♪ to make it last forever ♪
- It's unbelievable.
- [song fades]
[church bell tolling]
So, why'd you have to go
to Carlos for money?
It was either that
or my father would probably
sign the deal with the developer.
Developer?
Mm-hmm.
What's in it for them?
They want our docks.
They're putting a lot of pressure on him.
Now we don't have a lot of options.
That's a lot of responsibility.
Hmm.
There's the weight of
a hundred-year-old business
on my father's shoulders.
And on mine.
[pensive music playing]
[Julian] Watch your step.
This is where you live?
Yep. I've been living
on this boat for so long,
it's hard to fall asleep
without the sea underneath me.
Mm.
Was your mom ever around?
She... she died when I was eight.
I'm sorry.
Oh, here's the old man. [speaks Catalan]
Come here.
[in Catalan]
You have to meet Oriah.
Hello, Oriah.
- My son has told me a lot about you.
- [in English] In English, Dad.
[in English] I'm sorry.
- I'm Mateo.
- [Ry] Ry.
Nice to meet you.
Um, have we met before? You look familiar.
No, I don't think so.
It's my first time here.
- [Julian] Don't be weird.
- [Ry chuckles]
We were about to go for a ride.
Okay. Have fun.
Thank you. [chuckles]
Ready to work?
- [chuckles] Work?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
[♪ Paco Moreno sings "Cara Guapa"]
[Julian in Catalan] Listen up.
[Julian in English] This is Oriah.
She'll be helping out today, all right?
[in Catalan] You've never brought a girl
on board before.
[both chuckling]
- What'd he say?
- Nothing. Okay!
[in Catalan] Let's get to work.
[in English] Not the small ones, okay?
Okay, got it.
Why should they die if we can't eat them?
[chuckles softly]
You're a natural.
- Hmm.
- [both chuckle]
[song continues with lyrics in Spanish]
Good job.
[both chuckle]
I don't think I've ever smelled this bad
in my whole life.
Let's clean up, then.
[laughs]
[whoops, chuckles]
Come in.
The water is amazing.
Are there sharks in there?
Of course. It's the sea.
Come on!
I thought you didn't scare easily.
[Julian chuckles]
♪ ♪
[song continues with lyrics in Spanish]
[busy chatter]
Ah.
[chuckles]
Gràcies, Julian. [chuckles]
[in Catalan] You make your father proud.
Gràcies.
[song fades]
And now we get to enjoy
the fruits of our labor.
This is the best fish you'll ever try.
Mmm.
- Oh, my God, it is really good.
- See?
Mm-hmm. It's, like, sweet and buttery.
And good for you, too.
[both chuckle]
Mmm.
You really love what you do, don't you?
What's not to love? [chuckles]
I get to live on the sea,
- [chuckles]
- work alongside my family,
swim, fish.
I get to honor my dad,
my grandpa.
I've never even met my dad.
- Really?
- Yeah.
He's a businessman from Texas
that couldn't be bothered.
- [chuckles softly]
- But my mom is awesome.
She left Mallorca to pursue the...
the American dream.
When she arrived to the States,
she had nothing.
But she worked her ass off, and...
...what she's accomplished
is pretty amazing.
She's had a lot of success and...
- [chuckles]
- What?
I'm so sorry, but...
it just surprise me sometimes
what Americans define as success.
What do you mean?
I mean, it seems like
you just work and work
- [chuckles]
- just to go on vacation
and then buy more and more and...
I don't know. Look at our lives here.
Mm-hmm.
Sure, we have problems,
but we are more than happy
with what we have.
What else could we want?
Even Miss America ended up on my boat.
Sometimes you just
have to enjoy what you have
while you have it.
Does that make sense?
More than you know.
Being here...
...this place, this summer, it's...
really made me think about
where I want to be.
Well...
there's never been anywhere else on Earth
I want to be than right here.
[whispers] Can I see your room?
[♪ Love Spells sings "Love Costs"]
♪ You could never die ♪
♪ I'll always keep you alive ♪
♪ Think about you all the time ♪
♪ My security in life ♪
♪ And when I'm low ♪
♪ you get me high like coke ♪
♪ How could I let you go? ♪
♪ I'll never know ♪
♪ You could play me like a song ♪
♪ and I'll still sing along ♪
♪ The only tune I know...
[breathing heavily]
♪ Love you till we're bones ♪
♪ What else can I say? ♪
♪ Another time maybe ♪
♪ And I don't got the heart ♪
♪ to leave you in this way ♪
♪ Another heartbreak ♪
♪ The cycle breaks me ♪
♪ I have myself to blame ♪
♪ for hurting in this way ♪
♪ You could play me like a song ♪
- ♪ and I'll still sing along ♪
- [breathing heavily, moaning]
♪ Hold you till we're bones ♪
[song fades]
[Lena] Okay, um, do you mind having--
Oh. Hi.
- How are you feeling?
- Great.
You look radiant and happy.
I am.
Okay, I don't want to know.
As long as you're being safe.
You don't know
these Spanish boys like I do.
Had I stayed on this island,
Lord knows how many brothers
and sisters you'd have.
[laughs] Mom, please.
Uh, if you have a second,
I would love to talk to you
about the dance company.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- [Lena] Sorry.
[Isolde] Oh, no,
I don't like it. That one.
- That one.
- Okay, okay, we'll change it.
Wait. Do you know the Garcias?
Yeah. That's the company we're buying.
I thought you had all the land you needed.
Yeah, the Garcias own
some of the most valuable docks
- on the island.
- And we can't build the hotel
unless we buy them.
That's the boy you're seeing?
A Garcia?
- Lena, can I get the room?
- Of course.
Excuse me. Would you just mind
following me and showing me...
- Honey, I--
- No, Mom, please don't do this.
I know the situation. Don't--
Honey, this is for the best, okay?
Their business is...
- it's over.
- No, it's not.
They're just waiting for a loan.
They need more time.
Another loan?
That is just gonna put them
further into debt.
I'm giving them independence. Okay?
Freedom from being trapped
inside a failing business.
But they're not trapped though.
They love it here. They love what they do.
To them, it's just...
it's not about money.
It's so much more than that.
It's family, and it's where they're from.
No, I know. I know the Garcias.
And I feel for them.
Okay? I do.
But between you and I,
I offered them double
than what it's worth.
I'm not the villain here.
Mateo Garcia is never gonna have to work
another day in his life, nor his son.
It's not about that.
This is what makes them happy.
Mom, this gives them purpose.
[chuckles] You know,
it's easy to be idealistic, okay?
But business is business.
It's-it's not personal.
Please.
For me.
Okay, look, I'll see what I can do,
but I'm not promising anything, okay?
- [♪ Esha Tewari sings "In Twos"]
- ♪ I'll catch the train again ♪
♪ Starry-eyed
and I'm stalking your mind...
Can I talk to you about something?
♪ The light that you lead home ♪
♪ Drink a jug...
Can we just have one day
where we forget it all?
Please?
- Yeah.
- [song ends]
[uplifting music playing]
♪ ♪
- [Isolde] Ry, sweetie?
- [knock on door]
Are you here? Hey.
I have meetings all day,
but I wanted to see you before I left.
Did you refill your meds? Oh.
I got you two dresses,
this green and pink,
so let me know which one
you want to wear to the fundraiser.
Did you figure something out
for the Garcias?
Not yet, but I am working on it, okay?
[knock on door]
[Lena] Sorry, we're running late.
Yeah, here.
I'm gonna be busy today,
but why don't we have breakfast tomorrow.
You feeling okay?
You look a little pale.
I'm good.
Okay. I love you.
See you later.
[door opens, closes]
[phone chimes and vibrates]
[gentle music playing]
[Julian] Do you trust me?
Yeah.
Turn off the light.
Okay.
This... is my favorite feeling.
You just melt into everything around you.
It helps me forget about the problems
when the lights are on.
It's good to face your fears, Oriah.
How else can you overcome them?
♪ ♪
[♪ Levitation Room sings "Pienso en Ti"]
[seagulls squawking]
This is where we met. [chuckles]
Wait here.
[song continues with lyrics in Spanish]
If you can't swim, I can help you.
[Julian chuckles]
♪ ♪
- [song fades]
- [phone ringing and vibrating]
[chuckles]
Hey.
[Chloe over phone] Why do you look
like you just got laid?
- [Ry laughs]
- Okay, spill the tea.
Let's just say we have
a lot of catching up to do.
What is happening on that island?
Tell me everything.
Dude, I think I'm in love.
[chuckles] Like, on a cellular level.
On a cell-- Who even are you right now?
- [laughs]
- Okay, what-what are you gonna do?
Aren't you coming home
in a couple of days?
I don't know.
Wow.
So this is serious?
Romeo and Juliet serious.
Wait, didn't one of them die?
- [knock on door]
- [Lena] Hey, it's Lena.
- I have to go.
- [Chloe] Okay, talk soon. Call me.
Yeah?
Hi, Ry. Your mom's
not gonna make it this morning.
- [door closes]
- With the event tonight,
she's being pulled
in a million directions.
Look, I know it's not my place to say...
but...
the Garcias have agreed to sell.
They're signing with Redwyn now.
- What?
- I'm so sorry, Ry.
I have to go.
[line ringing]
[Julian speaking Spanish
in voicemail recording]
[phone beeps]
[panting]
[grunts]
[tense music playing]
No.
[exhales sharply]
Julian!
Julian, what happened?
Who did this?
It was Carlos.
Last night.
Now my father...
It was the final straw.
He signed with Redwyn.
It's all my fault.
No.
No, it's not.
Julian, my mom works for Redwyn.
I'm so sorry. I just found out--
You need to leave, Ry.
- What? But I just--
- Leave!
Leave.
[sniffles]
Mom?
Mom, what happened?
Could you give me a moment? Thank you.
You promised you would help them.
Honey, I did.
They had a sinking business,
and I threw them a lifeline.
[chuckles] Oh, so now
they have money and things
and no pride and no roots, just like you.
What does that mean?
It means you measure everything
with money.
You love power.
You're this power suit boss.
[stammers] You brought me
to where you're from,
and you've barely left the hotel.
Why do you even do all of this?
Why?
Why do I do this? I do this for you.
How do you not see that?
You think I like being busy all the time?
Of course I want to spend time with you.
But I also thank God every day
that I have this job,
which I'm really good at,
because that means
I can take care of you, Ry.
In every way that you need.
You're my purpose.
Okay? So...
If I could've changed
the outcome for the Garcias,
I would have.
Believe me, I would have.
[sighs]
So let's... let's just
take a deep breath...
...and get ready for the gala.
It is such an important night.
We only have a few days left here,
and I need you.
[pensive music playing]
[sighs]
[exhales heavily]
[taking off shoes]
[sniffles]
[inhales sharply]
[sighs]
[exhales shakily]
[whimpers]
[sobbing]
[sniffles]
♪ ♪
Oh.
I know you were having,
like, a super intense
mirror stare-off thing with yourself,
but for the record, you look hot.
And none of this is your fault,
by the way.
This is just the way the world works.
If it wasn't you guys,
it would've just been somebody else.
- [sighs]
- Hmm?
[whispers] Probably uglier.
- [laughs]
- Julian will come around.
[whispers] I promise.
[band playing "Tangos de la Juderia"]
- [lively chatter]
- [music continues]
[Isolde talking indistinctly under music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter continues]
[insects trilling]
[sighs]
No.
Fucking chemicals.
[grunts]
[panting]
[calling whistle]
[speaking Catalan]
What do you want?
You know...
your boyfriend... [smacks lips]
he owes me a lot of money.
And since you seem so fond
of his beautiful face,
I thought you'd like to stop me
from ruining it, no?
You'll get your money.
Slow down, reina.
Not everything has to be about cash.
- Some things are worth more than money.
- [whimpers]
Like food, wine, women.
Get off of me.
[panting]
If you touch her again, I'll kill you.
You understand?
Your money.
Shame.
She would have been fun.
Now get the fuck out of here!
You've got no reason
to come near us again.
Sure.
Until next time.
[laughs]
- You okay? You okay?
- I'm okay.
- You sure?
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Nice slap, by the way.
[both laughing]
Remind me to never make you mad.
[chuckles]
I'm really sorry about
not telling you about my mom.
I really thought I could fix it.
[quietly] It's okay.
It's not your fault.
[gentle music playing]
- [laughs]
- [chuckles]
Your dress.
It's ruined.
[chuckles] I was passing on
your ecological complaint.
[Julian chuckles]
That whole thing about the grass
and the chemicals.
- Wow.
- [laughs]
- [Julian] I need you now.
- [moans]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[music tempo quickens]
[Ry exhales heavily]
[Julian chuckles]
[breathing heavily]
- [grunts]
- [sighs]
[breathing heavily]
[moaning]
[Isolde speaking indistinctly]
[lively chatter and music]
[speaking Spanish]
[Amara] Cheers.
- [phone vibrates]
- [scoffs softly]
[♪ Buscabulla sings "Tártaro"]
[Amara] Yeah.
It never ceases to amaze
what rich people will leave behind.
That lost and found is a treasure trove.
How do I look?
[laughs]
I'll see you guys down there.
[song continues with lyrics in Spanish]
♪ ♪
I'm just wondering if there's a way.
I agree, but I'm worried
that it's too late.
You ready?
Let's do it.
[Ry] Mom?
I want to introduce you to Julian Garcia.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Señora Pera.
I've heard a lot about you.
Let me get you both a drink.
Did you tell him who I am
and my association with Redwyn?
[softly] Yeah.
Did you tell him about your epilepsy?
Gracias.
[applause]
Buenas noches. Good evening.
Thank you all for-for being here with us
to celebrate
this exciting new chapter for Mallorca.
We are thrilled to introduce
an arts center that will
preserve the cultural heartbeat
of this beautiful island.
Now, some of you know I grew up here,
a long time ago,
so it's nice to have a chance
to be able to give back,
and not only with this amazing arts center
but by bringing
a world-class resort to Mallorca.
So let's raise a glass
and make a...
...and let's make a toast.
To Mallorca.
[crowd] To Mallorca.
[applause]
[lively chatter]
[band playing gentle guitar music]
Mateo.
¿Cómo estás?
It's really good to see you.
I never thought I would see you again.
It's been a long time.
Yes.
Um, look, I want to...
let you know that
none of this was personal.
Isolde...
everything between us is personal.
[chuckles softly]
I mean, I just want
to explain my intentions.
You don't need to explain anything.
I mean, you're right.
The island is changing,
and I can't keep it up anyways.
I tried.
I held on to my business
as long as I could.
But in the end...
- I just have one thing to ask of you.
- Yeah?
When you're building the hotel,
when you're shaping what comes next,
just don't forget about
what was here before.
I could never forget what was here before.
There is one good thing to come of this.
Maybe they will have the future
we never could.
Let's go.
This suit makes me feel like
I'm in a straitjacket.
[Ry chuckles]
[speaks Catalan]
Go be with your dad.
I'll find you later at the docks.
- See you later.
- Bye.
[gentle guitar music playing in distance]
I thought you said your stories about
growing up here would bore me.
[Isolde inhales deeply]
Mateo Garcia.
[Ry chuckles]
He was my first love.
We met when we were kids,
and as teenagers we couldn't...
stay away from each other.
He was the air I breathed
and the water I swam in.
[both chuckle]
We always talked about the future,
and we made plans and...
And then everything changed.
Your mom died.
I had never experienced a pain like that.
And every part of the island
just reminded me of her.
I had to leave. I had to escape.
Just wanted to get away. [sniffles]
I asked him to come with me.
I begged him.
[chuckles softly]
He didn't want to leave his family
or the business.
We wrote letters for years,
back and forth,
and then one day the letters stopped.
So when I found out
we were building this hotel
and buying the land,
I jumped at the chance to help him.
I wish you would have told me.
Yeah.
And now I'm just the face
that stole his family's dreams.
No. No.
- You did your best, Mom.
- [scoffs softly]
And he knows it.
Yeah.
[♪ Barzin sings "All the While"]
♪ All summer ♪
♪ your love burned alone...
Can we stay up tonight?
Mm-hmm.
I've never seen a sunrise.
- What do you mean?
- [chuckles]
From the water?
[whispers] From anywhere.
Well...
...I can get you
the best seat in the house.
- Hmm?
- Mm-hmm.
♪ Beside the girl ♪
♪ Did you wait for ♪
♪ something to change you? ♪
♪ All the while you wait ♪
♪ for your heart ♪
♪ for your heart to... ♪
Look.
♪ Wake up...
[gasps]
- ♪ For your heart ♪
- [chuckles]
♪ to wake up ♪
Thank you for saving
your first sunrise for me.
You can have all my firsts
and all my lasts.
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[exhales softly]
[song fades]
Mom, is everything okay?
When did you stop taking your meds?
A few days after we arrived.
They made me feel numb.
Mom, I needed a single summer
of feeling something.
I'm such an idiot.
I should have never left you alone.
- Stop. No.
- I should've stayed on top of you...
- It's my decision!
- ...to make sure you took your pills!
No. It's my decision.
You probably made everything worse!
[voice breaking] I don't care.
I don't care.
- I care.
- I don't.
Okay.
- What are you doing?
- Let's go. We're leaving.
No, no, we're not.
- We're leaving.
- No. No, please.
Mom, I saw the sun rise
for the first time.
You did? That's great.
I can feel things.
I can feel Julian touching me,
and I could feel the sea on my skin.
[laughs] At least there's something
worth remembering.
[sobs] I want to stay here.
I want to live.
You want to stay here?
Oh, you want to live.
Now you want to live.
For how long, Ry?
How long do you want to live?
We're leaving.
I told Lena to move up our flight.
No.
Pack your stuff, Ry. Let's go.
No, Mom.
No.
Ry!
- [panting]
- [tense music playing]
- [muffled] Ry!
- [heart beating rapidly]
Ry?
[audio continues distorted]
Ry, where are you going?
[gasping]
Ry? Ry!
[heart beating faster]
[whimpering]
- [grunting]
- [ears ringing]
Ry!
♪ ♪
- [Isolde] Move, move, move! Ry!
- [water rushing]
[audio continues clearly]
Hey, hey, hey. Shh.
It's okay. You're okay, baby. You're okay.
I'm right here. I'm right here.
Everything's gonna be okay.
[heart monitor beeping steadily]
[whispers] I'm here.
[chuckles] There you are.
[crickets chirping]
- [breathlessly] Hi.
- [Isolde] Hey. Perfect timing.
- [door closes]
- I'm gonna go get a coffee.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
[door opens]
Oh. There she is.
Girl, I was high-key worried.
I would've come earlier,
but my boss made me
do, like, actual work.
You kept all this on the DL.
Ah?
Epilepsy and tubers?
Not to be confused with tumors,
although they sound just as shit.
I'm sorry for the secrets.
I get it.
You were looking for fun.
Which is why you gravitated to me. Hmm?
Speaking of fun, where's Prisha?
Is she here?
No.
All good things must come to an end.
She went home?
Yeah. But would I do it again?
Hell yeah, baby.
- [ticking]
- [monitor beeping steadily]
[gentle music playing]
[Julian] What happened?
Are you hurt?
I have tuberous sclerosis.
Causes epilepsy.
I was born with it.
What-what can we do?
Is there, is there a treatment?
Yes and no.
Medication helps,
but it's never been consistent.
And when I got here,
I stopped taking it altogether.
Why?
[voice breaking] Because it made me
feel numb.
Julian, I don't want to feel numb anymore.
Is surgery an option?
Yes, but there's too much risk.
I could lose my memory.
So...
so would that be the worst thing?
You would be healthy.
Everything I know would be gone.
Why didn't you tell me any of this?
Because I wanted to figure it out...
...for myself...
...what I'm living for.
And it's this place.
It's...
It's watching my mom do what she loves.
It's watching Amara
try a new makeup trend.
It's sitting in a dark cave with you...
...because you make darkness
feel peaceful.
Losing those memories...
...or the ability to make new ones...
...that's worse than death.
♪ ♪
[Julian breathes deeply]
I love you, Oriah.
[Ry chuckles]
[voice breaking] I love you, too.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Ry?
[whispers] Ry.
Ry.
Ry!
No, no. Oriah!
Papá. Papá. Papá.
[speaking urgently]
Ry, please.
[pensive music playing]
[EMT] Faint pulse.
She stopped breathing at the scene
- but stabilized in transport.
- Stay with me, okay?
I'm gonna be here, okay?
[doctor] She's holding on, but barely.
Scans show her condition has progressed.
It's your decision,
but we would strongly recommend surgery.
I mean, what is there to think about?
Ry has never wanted surgery.
I've tried to convince her for years,
and she made me promise.
We can stabilize her,
keep her comfortable.
But without surgery,
her condition will deteriorate,
and it will just be a matter of time.
Isolde...
...I understand the risks,
and Oriah spoke to me about her wishes.
But while there is a chance
that we could save her
and a chance she could have
a normal life...
...I beg you to take it.
She was worried about losing
the best parts of her life.
But if this works,
her favorite memories will be
the ones ahead of her.
♪ ♪
[heart monitor beeping steadily]
[pensive music playing]
[Isolde] She has the same condition
my mother had.
I'm so sorry, Izzy.
Does she know?
That I gave her this...
horrible thing that's hurting her?
No, she doesn't.
She wouldn't blame you.
You know, I never planned to have a baby.
Wasn't on my list.
No.
If I remember correctly, you wanted
a mansion, three cars and a pony.
I never got the pony.
When I found out I was pregnant, I...
I felt like my life had purpose.
And I wanted her so bad.
And I thought I would just
take the chance.
And you have raised a strong young woman
and gave her a wonderful life.
So whatever happens, Izzy,
you have nothing to be ashamed of.
Hmm? Nothing.
[contemplative music playing]
♪ ♪
Hey, thanks for coming.
- No, of course.
- We have a lot of work to do.
Yeah, so we have a couple of solutions,
but they're pretty complex.
[conversing in Catalan]
I'll take that one.
♪ ♪
That is excellent news. Thank you.
- Julian.
- Isolde.
Hey. Sit down. Sit down.
I...
I have something that belongs to you.
♪ ♪
When I was eight,
I found my father's letters
to his first love.
I always wondered who they were for.
And now I know who Izzy is.
[sighs]
[inhales]
[Isolde sighs]
[Mateo] Hey, guys.
Hey.
- You speak to the doctor?
- Uh, no.
No, I-I, um...
I haven't. There's been no-no change
with that, but...
...there has been a... a new development.
So you found a new plot of land
to build the hotel?
I know how much your business
means to you.
And I thought it was too late, but it's...
it's never too late.
You were right.
This is my home.
And I should be protecting it.
So...
we are investing in your business.
[chuckles softly]
It's what Ry would want.
It's what I want.
I think...
we will need to get you
one of these shirts, too.
[both chuckle]
Thank you, Izzy.
Can't wait to work together.
♪ ♪
[in Catalan]
I like the boat.
- It's good.
- [phone vibrating]
One second.
Yes.
[in English] Ry's awake.
[in Catalan] She's awake!
Welcome back, sweetie.
[panting]
Ry.
[Ry] My memories come back to me
one by one.
I feel like I could touch him,
someone I used to know.
I wonder...
...will fate keep following me here?
What I once thought would be
my last summer,
my first and last sunrise...
[♪ sombr sings
"do i ever cross your mind"]
...ended up being the beginning
of my life.
[Julian] Hola.
I'm Julian.
♪ When you lay awake at night ♪
♪ do I ever cross your mind? ♪
♪ 'Cause you still cross mine ♪
♪ Do I ever cross your mind? ♪
♪ I have a photo of you in my bed ♪
♪ When I look at it, I smell your scent ♪
♪ and I can feel you breathing
down my neck ♪
♪ thinking you're weighing down my chest ♪
♪ I have a photo of you in my bed ♪
♪ When I look at it, I smell your scent ♪
♪ and I can feel you breathing
down my neck ♪
♪ thinking you're weighing down my chest ♪
♪ When you lay awake at night ♪
♪ do I ever cross your mind? ♪
♪ 'Cause you still cross mine ♪
♪ Do I ever cross your mind? ♪
♪ How did I see you every day ♪
♪ and then suddenly you weren't mine? ♪
♪ I can't wait to hold you ♪
♪ when this is over ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ I can't wait to hold you ♪
♪ when this is over ♪
♪ When you lay awake at night ♪
♪ do I ever cross your mind? ♪
♪ 'Cause you still cross mine ♪
♪ Do I ever cross your mind? ♪
[song ends]
[gentle music playing]
♪ ♪
[music ends]